수록된 영상은 소재의 상황에 따라 보거나 듣기 힘든 부분이 있을 수 있으니 양해 부탁드립니다.
This video may contain scenes that are hard to watch at or listen to. Please be careful if you have epilepsy.
용자 엑스카이저
Yuusha Exkaiser
안녕, TV 앞의 여러분. 나, 엑스카이저에 대해서는 이미 알고 있니?
Nice to meet you, everyone. I hope you all already know about me, Exkaiser, right?
당연히 알고 있지. 다들 그렇지요?
Of course we all do! You too, right?
그 목소리는 혹시 코우타니?
Is that you, Kouta?
정확해! 역시 엑스카이저! 날 목소리만으로 바로 알아보잖아.
That's right! That's the Exkaiser I know! You figured out that it's me just by my voice!
당연하지, 코우타. 너와 나는 앞으로도 지구의 평화를 지켜 갈 동료니까.
Of course, Kouta. You and I are comrades, and we'll protect the peace on the Earth as we always did.
그런데 엑스카이저, 오늘은 여기에 있는 모두가 완전 놀랄 핫한 뉴스가 있어.
By the way, Exkaiser, I have a hot news for everyone here, which will surprise all of them!
발표해도 되지?
Mind if I tell them?
설마 코우타, 그 뉴스는 우리 카이저스의 변형 합체에 대한 거니?
Kouta, is it about transformations and combinations of us, Kaisers?
맞았어! 카이저스 변형 합체의 비밀에 대한 거야.
You're right! It's about Kaisers' transformations and combinations.
잠깐만, 코우타. 그건 아직 너무 일러.
Wait a moment, Kouta. It's too early for that.
그래? 그럼 난 뭐 해야 해?
Is that so? Then what should I do now?
알았어, 알았어. 코우타, 그럼 여기 있는 모두에게는 몰래 알려주기로 하자.
Okay, okay. Kouta, then let's explain only to our guests in secret.
좋아!
Yay!
그럼 코우타, 둘이서 소개하는 것으로 하자.
Then, Kouta, we'll explain to them by us two.
카이저스 변형 합체의 비밀
Kaisers' Secrets of Transformation and Combination
먼저 우주 경찰 카이저스의 합체 로봇 용사를 보자.
First, please take a look at the combiner robot heroes of Kaisers, the Space Police.
여기는 블루 레이커와 그린 레이커가 좌우합체해 변형한 울트라 레이커다.
This is Ultra Raker, formed by performing Left Right Fusion of Blue Raker and Green Raker.
이건 나, 엑스카이저와 킹 로더가 거대합체해 변형한 킹 엑스카이저.
This is me, King Exkaiser, formed by performing Giant Fusion of Exkaiser and King Loader.
여기는 맥스 팀 3인이 삼체합체해 변형한 갓 맥스다.
This is God Max, formed by performing Triple Fusion of the 3 members of Max Team.
어때, 셋 다 지금까지의 변형 합체 로봇보다도 훨씬 멋지지?
How was that? You'd find that we look much more stunning than the transforming combiner robots before us.
그럼 다음은 코우타가 변형 합체 방법을 순서대로 설명해 줄 거야.
And now, Kouta will explain how to transform and combine.
알았어, 엑스카이저. 이번엔 내가 변형 합체 방법을 설명해 드릴게요.
Got it, Exkaiser. I'll explain how to do those stuff.
좌우합체 울트라 레이커
Left Right Fusion: Ultra Raker
그럼 지금부터 좌우합체 방법을 설명하겠습니다.
From now on, I will explain how to perform Left Right Fusion.
먼저 블루 레이커와 그린 레이커로 변형하는 방법.
First, you would have to transform them into Blue Raker and Green Raker.
신칸센의 좌우 판을 벌립니다.
Unfold the plates on the side of the Shinkansen.
신칸센의 앞을 90도 앞으로 내립니다.
Turn down the front of Shinkansen by 90 degrees.
신칸센의 아래에서 몸 부분을 꺼내, 로봇 머리를 세웁니다.
Take out the body part under the Shinkansen, and raise the robot head.
머리를 회전하세요.
Rotate the head.
좌우의 동체를 180도 앞으로 회전시켜, 팔을 꺼내고, 어깨를 내립니다.
Turn both sides of the body by 180 degrees, take out the arms, and take down the shoulders.
양팔을 똑똑히 하세요.
Don't forget to do so for both sides.
발을 펴고, 검은 부분을 바깥으로 접어 구부립니다.
Unfold the right foot, and turn up the black part to the far side.
발끝을 꺼냅니다.
Take out the right toe.
역시 양쪽 다 하세요.
Do the same for the other side.
이걸로 신칸센에서 블루 레이커, 그린 레이커로 변형은 완료에요.
That would complete the transformation from Shinkansen to Blue Raker and Green Raker.
다음은 드디어 로봇 상태에서 좌우합체하는 방법을 보여드릴게요.
Next, I'll explain how to perform Left Right Fusion from robot modes.
발 부분을 아래로 내립니다.
Turn the foot down.
발끝 부분도 내립니다.
Turn the toe down, too.
양쪽 발에 해야 해요.
Do the same for the other foot.
팔을 올리고, 어깨 판의 뒤 안에 넣습니다.
Raise the right arm, and put it inside the space behind shoulder plate.
양팔에 해야 해요.
Do the same for the other arm.
몸을 180도 뒤로 회전시켜, 어깨 판을 몸의 뒤에 끼워 넣습니다.
Turn the body by 180 degrees, and put the shoulder plates to the back of the body.
이것도 양쪽에 해야 해요.
Make sure that you do that for both sides!
로봇 머리를 회전시켜 신칸센 안으로 넣어,
Rotate the robot head and put it inside Shinkansen.
상체였던 부분을 세워 어깨로 하고, 몸통를 만들어 발끝과 발꿈치를 꺼냅니다.
Raise the torso to make it as a shoulder, make the body, and take out the toes and heels.
블루 레이커와 그린 레이커를 좌우를 주의하면서 합체시킵니다.
Combine Blue Raker and Green Raker, making sure that they're on the other sides.
가슴과 머리를 붙이면 완성입니다.
Connect the chest and head, and it's complete.
이게 좌우 합체 울트라 레이커로 합체하는 방법이에요. 여러분도 금방 할 수 있어요.
That was how you make them perform Left Right Fusion to make them into Ultra Raker. Wasn't that easy?
이야, 코우타, 너는 이 나도 놀라게 하는구나. 이렇게나 변형 방법을 마스터하고 있을 줄이야.
Wow, Kouta, you're surprising me! You really have mastered the transformation sequences.
당연하지!
Of course!
그럼 이번엔 내가 킹 엑스카이저로의 거대합체와, 갓 맥스의 삼체합체, 필살기 브레스트 체인지를 소개하도록 하자.
This time, let me explain the Giant Fusion to King Exkaiser, God Max's Triple Fusion, and his specialty move Breast Change.
거대합체 킹 엑스카이저
Giant Fusion: King Exkaiser
평상시에는 코우타 집에서 자동차로 변신하고 있는 나 엑스카이저가 킹 로더와 거대합체해 킹 엑스카이저가 돼.
Usually, I am a car in Kouta's house, but when I have to, I, Exkaiser, combine with King Loader to form King Exkaiser.
이야, 역시 킹 엑스카이저는 멋져!
King Exkaiser is really cool!
다음은 삼체합체야.
The following will be about Triple Fusion.
삼체합체 갓 맥스
Triple Fusion: God Max
보통 제트기, 레이싱 카, 드릴 전차인 -스카이- 맥스 팀이 각각 로봇으로 변형.
The members of -Sky- Max Team are each a jet, a racing car, and a drill tank, and they'll transform into respective robots.
게다가 3체합체해서 갓 맥스가 돼.
Moreover, they perform Triple Fusion to become God Max.
3체합체도 대단해!
Triple Fusion is pretty cool, too!
다음은 우리 필살기를 봐 줘.
Next, take a look at our specialty moves.
필살기 브레스트 체인지
Specialty Move: Breast Change
나 엑스카이저와 스카이 맥스, 대시 맥스, 드릴 맥스의 가슴 부분이 필살 무기가 되는 것이 필살기 브레스트 체인지.
Chest parts of me, Exkaiser, Sky Max, Dash Max and Drill Max become a powerful weapon by doing our specialty move Breast Change.
딱 봐도 강해 보이지?
You know it's strong just by looking at.
어때, 코우타? 이게 카이저스 변형 합체 비밀의 전부야.
How was that, Kouta? That was all about the secret of transformation and combination of Kaisers.
응, 대단해, 엑스카이저. 나도 모르는 비밀까지 잘 알고 있구나.
It was awesome, Exkaiser! You know all the secrets that even I don't know!
그래. 아, 코우타, 여기서 지금부터 모두가 가지고 놀 수 있는 상품을 소개해 줘.
Sure I do. Oh, right, Kouta, please tell them about our merchandises that everyone can play with.
알았어, 엑스카이저. 그럼 제가 모두에게 소개할게요!
Got it, Exkaiser. Then, let me tell all of you about those!
좌우합체 블루 레이커 2400엔
Left Right Fusion: Blue Raker: 2400 yen
동해도 신칸센이 로봇으로 변형! 블루 레이커!
Transforming Tokaido Shinkansen Robot! Blue Raker!
좌우합체 그린 레이커 2400엔
Left Right Fusion: Green Raker: 2400 yen
동북 신칸센이 로보트로 변형! 그린 레이커!
Transforming Tohoku Shinkansen Robot! Green Raker!
좌우합체 울트라 레이커 4800엔
Left Right Fusion: Ultra Raker: 4800 yen
블루 레이커, 그린 레이커 두 대가 좌우합체! 울트라 레이커!
Left Right Fusion of Blue Raker and Green Raker! Ultra Raker!
거대합체 킹 엑스카이저 4월 말 발매 예정 5800엔 (미확정)
Giant Fusion: King Exkaiser: To be released by the end of April: 5800 yen (preliminary)
엑스카이저와 킹 로더가 세트로 있어서, 거대합체가 가능한 킹 엑스카이저!
Exkaiser and King Loader are in one set, so that you can do Giant Fusion! King Exkaiser!
삼체합체 스카이 맥스 4월 발매 예정 2000엔 (미확정)
Triple Fusion: Sky Max: To be released by April: 2000 yen (preliminary)
제트 전투기에서 로보트로 변형! 스카이 맥스!
Transforms from a fighter jet into a robot! Sky Max!
삼체합체 대시 맥스 4월 발매 예정 1800엔 (미확정)
Triple Fusion: Dash Max: To be released by April: 1800 yen (preliminary)
레이싱 카에서 로보트로 변형! 대시 맥스!
Transforms from a racing car into a robot! Dash Max!
삼체합체 드릴 맥스 4월 발매 예정 2000엔 (미확정)
Triple Fusion: Drill Max: To be released by April: 2000 yen (preliminary)
드릴 전차에서 로보트로 변형! 드릴 맥스!
Transforms from a drill tank into a robot! Drill Max!
삼체합체 갓 맥스 4월 발매 예정 5800엔 (미확정)
Triple Fusion: God Max: To be released by April: 5800 yen (preliminary)
스카이 맥스, 대시 맥스, 드릴 맥스가 삼체합체해서 갓 맥스로!
Sky Max, Dash Max, and Drill Max do Triple Fusion to become God Max!
코우타. 이 외에도 내 무기도 있지?
Kouta. There should be my weapons too, right?
그랬지! 그 외에도 즐거운 상품이 더 있어.
You're right! We have more fun products, too.
계속해서 설명할게요!
Let me explain more!
카이저 브레이스
Kaiser Brace
버튼을 누르면 소리하고 빛이 나는 카이저 브레이스!
By pressing buttons, you get lights and sounds! Kaiser Brace!
카이저 브레이스 3월 발매 예정 1980엔 (미확정) 건전지 포함
Kaiser Brace: To be released by March: 1980 yen (preliminary): batteries included
카이저 브레이스! 너도 이걸로 엑스카이저를 부르자!
Kaiser Brace! Try calling Exkaiser using it from now on!
카이저 소드
Kaiser Sword
여덟 가지 소리와 빛이 나는 카이저 소드!
Eight kind of sounds and lights! Kaiser Sword!
카이저 소드 3980엔 건전지 별매
Kaiser Sword: 3980 yen: batteries not included
카이저 소드! 너도 썬더 플래시로 파워업해 보자!
Kaiser Sword! Try Powering Up with Thunder Flash!
어때, 엑스카이저? 대단하지!
How was that, Exkaiser? Wasn't it awesome?
그래, 꽤나 괜찮은 상품 라인업이구나. 이래서는 TV에서 우리도 멍하니 있을 수는 없겠어, 코우타.
Yeah, it was a pretty good merchandise lineup. We really have to do even better from now on, Kouta.
맞아.
Agreed.
우리도 TV에서 힘낼 테니까, 여러분도 상품이 발매되면 꼭 가지고 놀아 줘.
We'll do our best on the television, so please play with the merchandises when they get released.
그럼 코우타, 슬슬 떠날 시간인 것 같구나.
Now, Kouta, it seems that it's time to go.
알았어, 엑스카이저.
Got it, Exkaiser.
그럼 마지막으로 여러분에게는 오늘 소개한 상품을 보여주는 것으로 인사를 할게.
Finally, for all of you, let me show you the products that we've introduced today.
여러분은 다시 TV에서 보자. 그럼, 코우타, 가자!
We'll meet you again on the television. Then, Kouta, let's go!
오케이!
OK!
비디오에서 나온 상품 가격은 전부 표준소매가 (세금 포함)입니다.
All the prices of products from the video are tax included.
또한 상품 색이나 크기, 디자인 등은 바뀌는 경우가 있으니 양해 부탁드립니다.
Also, please understand that the colors, sizes, or designs may change when released.
용자 엑스카이저
Yuusha Exkaiser